fujitsu-siemens.com 2010-06-08

# Privacy policy - Fujitsu

---  
| |   
  
## Fujitsu and your personal data  
  
As one of the leading providers of information products and technologies Fujitsu is committed to the use of state of the art technologies in order to continuously improve the services offered to our customers and to protect Personal Information of our customers and visitors of our web sites as effectively as possible. The term "Personal Information" comprises all information which allows or facilitates the identification of any individual. Fujitsu represents and warrants strictly to comply to any Data Protection laws or any other applicable laws. You may access the public web pages of Technology Solutions without entering any of your personal details. In a few cases, however, we or our partners will need certain information from you in order to give you better service. If you wish to give us such details (e.g. Name, Address, e-Mail) we will inform you about how the data will be used before you submit it. You can also request to see our public list of technical procedures.  
  
## Fujitsu and the security and quality of Information  
  
It is our intention to protect the quality and integrity of your personal data. For this we have made appropriate technical and organisational arrangements, for example providing the option to encrypt emails or personal data submitted to our websites. Fujitsu will take every care to carry out any corrections you want made to your data as quickly as possible. Your support, e.g. in making sure that requests for correction are returned to the sender's address, is invaluable.  
  
## Fujitsu and technologies used (Cookies, Web beacons)  
  
Occasionally we will collect information about visitors of our On-line services in order to improve our Internet Service and other On-line services as well as to be better able to meet the needs of our customers. However, this is done in a completely anonymous way and any identification of individuals is made impossible. We use so called Cookies to improve the quality of our service. Cookies are data elements, which are stored by your browser. Cookies help us to offer you specially tailored offers, should you visit our web sites again in the future. If you do not want Cookies to be stored on your browser, please adjust your browser accordingly. Information on how to adjust your browser can be found in the user documentation of your browser.

Nielsen//NetRatings and Google Analytics (a web analysis service of Google Inc. ("Google"), two independent companies for internet audience measurement and analysis, is using cookies and code which is embedded in the site, to gather non-personal data on our behalf, regarding the visitors to our site. Both the cookies and the embedded code provide only non-personal statistical information about visits to pages on the site, the duration of individual page view, paths taken by visitors through the site, data on visitors' screen settings and other general information. Fujitsu uses this type of information, as with that obtained from other cookies used on the site, to help improve the services to our users.

The information generated on base of Google by the cookie(s) about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States . Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage.  Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.  You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. 

If you wish to reject the use of cookies for the above stated purposes, Nielsen/NetRatings provide you with the respective options for changing or disabling the embedded code. For more information go to [direct.www.netratings.com/privacy.jsp?section=leg_scs](http://direct.www.netratings.com/privacy.jsp?section=leg_scs). If you should have any comments or questions about Nielsen//NetRatings, their privacy policy or the disabling/change options, please contact [webprivacy@netratings.com](mailto:webprivacy@netratings.com).  
  
## Fujitsu and data protection technologies  
  
New technical developments are enabling users to have more control over their personal data. Fujitsu is making every effort to provide you with suitable options whenever the nature of the data we are holding makes it necessary.  
  
## Fujitsu and child security  
  
The Fujitsu websites contain little if any information that is aimed directly at children. No Personal Information should be submitted to Fujitsu web sites by children without consent of their parents or guardian. Therefore we encourage all parents or guardians to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their Personal Information. We believe it is our responsibility to abide by all relevant laws and regulations Any breaches that come to light will be investigated and prosecuted by Fujitsu.  
  
## Legal notes  
  
## No guarantees for content  
  
Fujitsu web sites contain links to other web sites operated by third parties. Fujitsu strives to carefully select such web sites, however Fujitsu does not accept any liability for any content stored on such web sites nor does Fujitsu accept any liability for such third parties to comply with applicable data protection laws. All information on our Internet websites has been carefully checked by Fujitsu or our partners. Fujitsu and third parties involved cannot, however, guarantee that it is correct, complete or up to date.  
  
## No consulting  
  
The information on Fujitsu web pages does not represent individual consulting. For consulting work, please arrange a personal or telephone contact with one of our staff.  
  
## Use of Internet pages  
  
The content and layout of the Fujitsu Internet pages are protected intellectual property. Reproduction of the content in any form requires written permission from Fujitsu. 

In case of any question or comments please contact the Fujitsu Privacy Protection Officer.

As the Internet evolve, so will also evolve our Data Privacy Protection Policy. Changes to our Security and Data Protection Policy will be posted on this page.  
  
| | | |
